Hi, Luna Kamakagi of Tsukiyono speaking.
Oh yeah? Want to knock off the Akatsuki Syndicate's big boss?
Wake up, ladies! Time to clock in!
Grego Amagi!
Arisa Iteroi!
Kumari Mikagura!
Your dirty work is our slurdy work!
We're the Tsukiyono Company!
No!
This losing streak will be the death of me!
You're not a lucky fella, are ya, boss?
You just don't have the skills!
Junior! This clearly isn't the joking matter!
I'm not going home until I want to miss lunch!
Every day we watch these jerks eat such delicious food.
I had no idea it was an option to prepare a melon so beautifully.
All we ever get to eat are bean sprouts.
When I took this job, they swore to me that killers make a killing.
If that's the case, why can't I make rent?
Hold on! We have a job to do!
The target is toast, with this bad boy up-blowing the smithermons.
This one's so cool! Like a real assassin!
I may have stolen off the president's desk.
It's dry, right? It should ignite.
It lit up without any problems.
This could work.
Masu, komari thought.
Bad roll of the dice!
Lady Luck's not on our side!
I'm the Beastar!
That was fun!
And theaufen drive will another year
They will eat so well.
Can two Hor Pang make a fight!
And that will happen.
Oh
Despair, fool
And die
This thing's way too heavy for me
Oh, dear
Hey, I think it's hilarious
You likey?
It's so cute I could just explode
Tsukama's straight up genius for real
They even managed to make the Yakuza really cute
Junior's voice is way hot, but he's a total airhead
He's a fan fave
So what then? You wanna cosplay Junior?
Mm-mm, close-ish, but no cigar
I'm vibing with Orisha
My fingy
At first, she reads as the cool, collected type
But she's a bit of a ditz and has a heart of gold
Well, you two mean a lot to me
So, uh, could I call you my friend?
My obsession started in F1
Let me find the exact moment I fell in love
Bingo!
Are you done changing?
What mission could possibly warrant this outfit?
The boss is at the casino
You'll need to sneak in undercover
Her cute reaction sent me head over heels
Like, ask before you put it on, ya doof
Kitagawa knows all the lines by heart?
Pardon my girl math
But any show where the uniforms are bunny suits
Is a perfect ten
And Tsukam gets bonus points for the ditz on the stockings
Also, the jacket look is a multiplier
You mean the tail coat?
Guess so
Isn't it the cutest ever?
I didn't realize you liked bunny girls so much
Well, yeah, of course
Loving bunny girls unifies the masses
They're that popular?
I mean, I do see them pretty often on TV and in commercials
Yeah, duh!
Sometimes anime characters only ever wear regular outfits
But they still get bunny suit merch
Huh? That seems so random
Is that really allowed?
Yeah, no doi
It's a fact
Everyone with a pulse loves a bunny
People get creative
You see loads of different bunny variations on Halloween
Uh, right
But for character merch
It's almost always the old fashioned bunny costumes
Guess that makes sense
Bunny suits have taught me the valuable life lesson
That even though the new version of something
Can be innovative and exciting
Nothing will ever beat the OG
Oh, I see
Of course
The OG
Right
I get it now
Breakneck enlightenment
I'll finish watching the series tonight
Then start drafting some designs
For real?
That's kinda quick
Sure you're not pushing too hard?
I'm sure
I think I'm finally getting used to making outfits
I hope you're not fibbing
I wonder if there's something I could help with
Maybe we should take pics in a studio
Studio?
It's some kind of casino vibes
Please promise she'll show me the place before you make anything official
Hey!
I said sorry for all the weirdness last time
Now check this
Suzuka did a shoot there and sent some pictures
Whoa!
It's President Luna!
She nailed her energy
She looks so legit
She's basically the pros herself
You can tell from the photos that she's very careful about the details
It'd be cool if we could rent out that spot, huh?
Yeah!
That'd be great!
Oh!
Do you want one before they're gone?
May I?
Mm-mm!
I appreciate you
Oh!
Call and get her
Uh!
I don't know about this, Kitakawa
I...
I'm not so...
Uh...
JK dude
So not cool!
You really gotta stop teasing me like that!
Boopsy boopsy
Undercover at the eel shop
My hands are all slimy
Maybe we can use the slime to slip up the box
Ooh!
There you are, Maureen
Noah?
I looked everywhere for you
You totes ignored my message
Uh...
Sorry about that
Oh...
Well hello, Gojo
Sup, girl?
They were gonna talk about the Halloween party after we hit the cafeteria
Crap, you're mad?
I'll trade you a snackie for forgiveness
Get up, dude
It was rude, but I'm a grown-up, so I'm willing to let it slide, okay?
Thank you
I'm super sorry
See ya, Gojo
Talk to you soon
Alright
Let's go, Noah
Uh...
Would you be able to come over to my place tomorrow?
Uh, yeah!
Of course I'll come over
I love you
What does he want with me so out of the blue?
I usually just show up
Last time I got an invite was...
It was...
Never?
He...
He really wants to see me
Of course...
This is about the outfit, huh?
Yes
Oh, Boo. I thought you wanted to...
Forget it! I thought nothing at all!
I got hyped up because I thought he was inviting me over for a home date.
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
So, I was able to finish the other pieces, but the main bodysuit isn't quite working.
I made it to fish you perfectly in its line just like it is in the show.
There's just one big problem.
Look at this.
I have no idea why it keeps happening.
Please forgive me!
Take its chill pill, Gojo! We'll figure this out!
I've seen bunny suits that rely on clear straps to keep them in place.
Huh? That's really a thing?
Mm-hmm. We could place them here like it's a swimsuit.
Boom! Fixed it!
It falls down a lot in the animes, so I don't think they're using straps.
Got me there.
The waist has a bit of extra room, and while adding straps would fix our gravitational issue,
they would alter the silhouette entirely.
I want to fix it like this.
If the pro says so, then I totally agree.
I was working as a model one time and had a stylist drop the super-sage wisdom that if an outfit ever hides your curves,
you can clip it back to unleash some serious va-va-voom.
Uh... Clip?
Oof. You don't look too convinced.
For now, let's try the strap route.
They'll be practically invisible as soon as we button up the tailcoat.
And...
Frick, dude!
It's so cute!
Awesome work as always.
You killed it!
No surprise there.
Straps will be easy to find.
Let's go.
Right now?!
Of course.
Gotta get what I want, when I want.
Life's too short.
Come on!
Roll out!
Okay.
Now that's intense!
Pardon me.
Hmm?
Huh?
Yes?
Sorry to bother you, but I need some assistance.
Think you can help me?
Let's see what you got.
Ah!
You...
You're planning to make this?
To where?
Yes!
I sure am.
That was quick.
His eyes.
So pure and honest.
Times have changed.
Gender and age don't matter.
We should be free to wear whatever we want.
Our only limit now is our own creativity.
There's nothing wrong with this young man wearing a bunny suit.
And to think, this brave trailblazer has put his faith in me.
I'll help him.
For the good of mankind.
A bunny suit, eh?
With your lovely figure, you'll pull it off nicely.
Hmm?
Sorry.
The line for the bathroom was massive.
Did you find the straps?
I looked around, but I couldn't find them.
So I just asked this gentle...
I am terribly sorry.
What a mix-up.
My apologies, sir.
TBH, I'd love to see him in a bunny suit.
Togawa.
Just so you know, there is a way to secure a body suit without using pesky clear straps.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Shall I show you?
Yes, please.
The front, the back, and two more to support the chest area.
Add boning like a corset.
You see?
But here, it doesn't look like it's built with any real structure.
Sure, a simplified design to achieve an animated gag.
In real life, there'd be pads and boning, so no real risk of the top flipping or slipping off.
Hey, are you saying I'm not going to get any of Orisha's classic jiggle physics?
Uh, seems they traded fashion physics for a bit of humor.
It won't fall off of a three-dimensional lady.
That's a shame.
Why is she so disappointed?
You just construct it like a corset?
I've even built one of those before.
Yeah, and I've worn like a bajillion.
I was so confident that my design was perfect.
When you dwell on a problem and overthink it for too long, it's easy to ignore the answer that's right under your nose.
I think you're right.
I usually turn to the internet when I need help, but this time, I didn't even do that.
Lately, I haven't run into many problems I couldn't solve.
I let my hubris get to me.
It's fine, dude.
I'm such a failure!
It's not that big a deal.
Well, you're learning, so don't be so hard on yourself.
Mistakes are an important part of growth, so try to enjoy them.
Now let me get that boning for you.
Boning is OP!
This stuff is the shit!
Now it's complete.
I'm in love!
Are you ready?
Do you want to try it on?
Sir, yes, sir!
I got way too cocky.
I hope this attempt goes better.
Hey, Gojo?
Uh-huh?
It totally fits me.
And, uh, the top is staying up, but there's one problem.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'll fix it right...
Uh, uh, uh...
Uh, since it's so high-cut...
Uh, you see, my panties sort of came out to say hello.
What do you think we should do?
Whoa!
Don't ditch me now!
My neon's hot, so I was high-cut too, but I wear a quick suit!
This is new territory!
I don't think I can go, Commando Bro!
I can really use your expertise!
I'm no expert!
I've never worn a bunny suit!
Party-lar-lar!
No time for jokes!
I'm cheeks-out over here!
Yeah, I know!
So please don't open the door!
It's called Studio Macaron Night, right?
Yep!
It's like Suzuka's sexiest spot.
She gave us our location and that sick makeup tip, too.
I can't believe I never thought to do your makeup at home to save some time.
Pardon us.
This rules!
Look at this place!
There are all sorts of different sets we can use.
Check your go-jo!
Is this giving bougie or what?
Definitely!
It'll make for some great photos.
I'm so happy we came here!
Okay, time to get bunny-fied.
Right.
I understand why cosplayers are so picky about their backgrounds.
It's an important piece of the puzzle that can really capture the character's world.
The same goes for Hina dolls.
The screens and paper lanterns make all the difference.
It's an absolute must.
Oh, real quick.
The high-cut stuff bugs you, yeah?
No, that's not true!
It made you mega-super-grouchy last time.
Please forgive me if the swimsuit is perfectly adequate!
I wouldn't exactly call that mood grouchy.
I think antsy is a better word, but I should be okay if I concentrate.
Oh, yeah?
Well, if you're interested, I thought of a solution to keep it more peachy.
You really did?
I need my photographer firing on all cylinders today.
Thank you so much for being so considerate.
Epic!
I knew the code would be fire!
It fits perfectly!
I'm snatched, but I can still move as much as I want!
And this adhesive underwear is seriously brilliant!
No panty lines for me!
And check it!
I'm seriously losing my mind over this quirky tail action!
It's just so precious, I could scream!
I feel it!
I'm totally Arisha right now!
Huh?
What's with the face?
Aren't you excited?
Of course!
But where's the peachy?
Ah.
Under the black stockings?
I'm wearing skin-colored tights!
My legs look exposed!
But they're covered!
Cool, huh?
Wakana Gojo.
Fifteen years old.
Teenager.
In his eyes,
the skin was as bare as ever.
Time to shoot!
You...
look great.
Nice job.
So what?
Hot stuff?
Uh, yeah.
Cute?
Yes.
Yes!
Killing it!
Um, yes.
Hmm.
This is bad.
I can't concentrate at all.
I want to capture Arisha's coolness,
but I'm getting way more than that!
Gojo!
Let's use this Chinese-looking background.
It'll look so gnarly!
Yeah, all right.
Yay!
China!
Whoa!
The details are insanely pretty!
It's getting me so hyped up!
Focus, focus, focus!
Are you good?
I'm sorry.
Can we take a quick break?
Peke!
I'll check out the pics.
Oh my gosh!
They turned out great!
I'm gonna pee my pants.
The only whack detail is the stockings I picked.
In the anime, they don't have this gap.
This was my first time trying them out.
I adore Arisha,
but Komarin wears the cutest tights by far.
I think those lines running down the back
are essential with a bunny suit.
I wonder why they look so sick.
I agree that those lines fit the outfit nicely,
but I haven't looked at many other bunny suits.
Are they really so special?
Of course they are!
I make a truck ton of difference!
No lines.
Lines.
See?
The lines revolutionize the look.
What in the world is she showing me?
It's night and day!
Come on, you agree!
You see?
I guess so.
You see it?
I want to try wearing cute tights like these
as soon as possible.
Maybe I'll put my own spin on a bunny.
I'm so smart!
I'll wear them to the holo party!
Holo what?
You mean like Halloween?
Yeah!
It'll just be a hangout with the usual crew.
Hey!
You should come with and dress up!
Huh?
Let's cosplay!
Alright, big smile!
Let's go.
Those crowds blew!
For real, I guess everyone else is still caught up in them.
Snacky time is calling my name.
After all those crowds, I'd prefer nap time.
Can we get a party set, a combo pizza, and some fries to see?
I'm glad you boys decided to come with.
You're saving Maureen from all the randos that fit on her.
She could just ignore them, but she started growling instead.
Huh? She's scary as hell!
Do you wanna sing, Yodo?
I'm sorry, I don't know many songs.
The theme from Flower Princess Blaze and Slippery Pure Heart
are kind of all I have in my repertoire right now.
More core?
Let's get you behind a mic.
Uh...
No.
More songs!
Hey!
Sure you didn't wanna get in the pic?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
You should've cosplayed, Junior.
Like you would've been perfect as him!
No! I'm cool with this!
Well, I guess your look is more traditional Halloween anyway.
When we were taking pictures outside,
everyone kept saying how cute you looked, Maureen.
Oh, they did?
Wait! That love wasn't meant for me?!
Yeah, no.
You're kidding!
Tonight was my only chance to get picked up by somebody who wasn't I!
Is that the reason you agreed to hang out with us?
He does like him older.
I came to see all the different cosplays.
It's certainly been great for research, but...
I wonder how they all feel about me tagging along.
Is it really okay for me to be here with them?
Mm-hmm.
If anyone complimented me, it's thanks to my outfit!
It rocks!
You're the one rocking it, girl!
Is it true that you made it for her, Gojo?
Uh...
Yes!
That is madness!
I thought she bought it!
Her makeup is fire, too!
When you sent that goth Lolita pic, I couldn't tell it was you.
She's a Kutana!
You look like a different person.
Your face totally changes when someone else puts on your makeup.
People who see me in magazines don't even recognize me!
Uh...
Hey, Gojo.
You do Kitakawa's cosplay makeup, yeah?
Uh...
How the heck do you know how?
You're a guy.
That's a girl thing.
Isn't it?
Men can do it just as easy.
Remember my older brother?
Oh, I forgot him!
Does your brother wear guy-liner or something, Shiki?
He's in cosmetology school.
He has classes on, like, nail art and makeup.
It's all about your talent.
For sure.
There are loads of male makeup artists.
You're right!
I've seen him online!
Plus, they're his family from the Hina doll shop!
He's great at makeup because he practices painting their faces!
Uh...
Tukawa!
Wait a second!
Do you live in Iwatsuki?
They took us to that shop in grade school and it blew my freakin' mind!
Toast dolls are genius work!
I know, right?
The brushes they use are teeny!
You can't properly appreciate that until you've seen them in person!
I'm sure you're right, but you're breaking my eardrums.
Let's work on our volume control, Kensei!
Huh?
Why isn't anyone saying that I'm creepy?
I mean...
Maybe?
Maybe...
It was just known.
Maybe no one else sees a problem with it.
A full spread with Yoda is smelly!
Ha!
But...
It's really...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
Misty!
Of course!
Ha!
There was that much sacrifice that was really much Ortizot anime, такая song, Kensei!
He just moved!
Amour craft!
custom and the focus of làm Taikai!
Thank you.